leaf1 = [
{"question":"佈滿","Answer":"bù mǎn"},
{"question":"曲折","Answer":"qūzhé"},
{"question":"街巷","Answer":"jiēxiàng"},
{"question":"村莊","Answer":"cūnzhuāng"},
{"question":"窮困 ","Answer":"qióngkùn  "},
{"question":"小巷","Answer":"xiǎoxiàng"},
{"question":"躲避","Answer":"duǒbì"},
{"question":"顏料","Answer":"yánliào"},
{"question":"催討","Answer":"cuītǎo"},
{"question":"畫紙","Answer":"huàzhǐ"},
{"question":"債務","Answer":"zhàiwù"},
{"question":"畫布","Answer":"huàbù"},
{"question":"閣樓","Answer":"gélóu"},
{"question":"聚","Answer":"jù"},
{"question":"便宜","Answer":"piányi"},
{"question":"慕名","Answer":"mùmíng"},
{"question":"租金","Answer":"zūjīn"},
{"question":"蘇","Answer":"sū"},
{"question":"瓊斯","Answer":"qióngsī"},
{"question":"破舊","Answer":"pòjiù"},
{"question":"瓦磚","Answer":"wǎzhuān"},
{"question":"建築","Answer":"jiànzhù"},
{"question":"廉價","Answer":"chuāng"},
{"question":"信念","Answer":"xìnniàn"},
{"question":"患","Answer":"huàn"},
{"question":"肺炎","Answer":"fèiyán"},
{"question":"奄奄一息","Answer":"yǎnyǎnyīxī"},
{"question":"抵抗","Answer":"dǐkàng"},
{"question":"病魔","Answer":"bìngmó"},
{"question":"悄悄","Answer":"qiāoqiāo"},
{"question":"窗","Answer":"chuāng"},
{"question":"瓊斯","Answer":"qióngsī"},
{"question":"甩","Answer":"shuǎi"},
{"question":"走廊","Answer":"zǒuláng"},
{"question":"概","Answer":"gài"},
{"question":"原","Answer":"yuán"},
{"question":"激","Answer":"jī"},
{"question":"渴望","Answer":"kěwàng"},
{"question":"拿波里","Answer":"ná bōlǐ"},
{"question":"蘇","Answer":"sū"},
{"question":"投入","Answer":"tóurù"},
{"question":"提","Answer":"tí"},
{"question":"眼淚","Answer":"yǎnlèi"},
{"question":"住","Answer":"zhù"},
{"question":"故意","Answer":"gùyì"},
{"question":"夾","Answer":"jiā"},
{"question":"腋","Answer":"yè"},
{"question":"輕鬆","Answer":"qīng sōng"},
{"question":"哨","Answer":"shào"},
{"question":"窗 ","Answer":"chuāng  "}
]